b2cjewels.com 2006-10-19

# Diamond jewelry manufacturers,suppliers,exporters,sellers:rings,earring,pendants,necklaces,bracelets,fine jewelry.

B2C Jewels will occasionally update its privacy statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When B2C Jewels posts changes to this statement, you will see the word "Updated" next to the Privacy Policy link on the B2C Jewels home page. B2C Jewels encourages you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we are protecting your information. If you have questions or concerns about policy changes, you should first contact the B2C Jewels customer service department at [info@b2cjewels.com](mailto:info@b2cjewels.com) or 1 800 210 0223. 

**How We Use The Information We Gather**   
B2C Jewels may request personal information, including your name, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, credit card number, and expiration date. B2C Jewels collects that information in order to: 

  * Process an order 
  * Verify your identity for payment authorization 
  * Contact you regarding your order status 
  * Ship your order to you 
  * Send you news from B2C Jewels (if you request) 
  * Generate anonymous statistics 
  * Provide you with an excellent shopping experience 

Once B2C Jewels gathers your name and address, this information will then be transferred to your credit card company, if applicable, for confirmation to complete your purchase. Your name and address will not be used for any other purpose than delivery of your order. Your name and address will not be sold to mailing-list firms. Although B2C Jewels may occasionally share statistics about our customers with important business partners, we do not disclose any identifying information about individual customers. 

**Third Party Privacy Policies**   
B2C Jewels gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services that are detailed below. B2C Jewels will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect additional information that it needs to provide you with the requested service. B2C Jewels encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from B2C Jewels so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use, and share your information. B2C Jewels is not responsible for the privacy statements or content on Web sites outside of B2C Jewels's Web site. 

**Tracking of Advertising Links, Action Tags, and Cookies**   
B2C Jewels works with a third-party advertising company to collect information on advertisement performance and Web site usage. This company serves B2C Jewels ad banners on our behalf which use action tags and cookies to measure how many times users view and click on an ad and which specific pages of our Web site users visit (e.g. a registration or checkout page). To do so, this company may use information about your visits to the B2C Jewels Web site and other Web sites. Unless otherwise notified, our third-party advertising company does not use names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or telephone numbers and does not link any online actions or cookies to an identifiable person. The use of your cookies is subject to the privacy policy of our third-party advertising company. [To learn more about our third party advertising company visit their website.](http://www.philippimarketing.com/)

**Site Usage Tracking and Analysis**   
B2C Jewels, LLC. has contracted with a third party, Yahoo, Inc. and/or its authorized partner or reseller, to provide additional tracking and analysis of information and data collected from visitors to our Web site. No uniquely identifiable information is tracked by Yahoo. Yahoo does not use names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or telephone numbers and does not link any online actions or cookies to an identifiable person. B2C Jewels, LLC. reserves the right to provide that information and data to Yahoo, Inc. and/or its authorized partner or reseller for those purposes. 

**B2C Jewels Communication**   
B2C Jewels offers customers many ways to keep up to date with the latest product offerings and promotions. Below, we outline how we treat the information you provide to B2C Jewels. 

**Email Newsletters**   
B2C Jewels offers customers the chance to opt-in to receive regular updates, news, and special offers via email. Customers may opt-out of receiving these newsletters at anytime. 

**Surveys  
** B2C Jewels occasionally requests information from our users and customers via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, and all participants have a choice whether or not to disclose information. The requested information typically includes the customer's first name, as well as information relating to the customer's experience at B2C Jewels, or their opinions on products they have purchased. Survey information will be used internally to monitor or improve this site, and after attaining user permission, may be posted on the site to provide information about our products to other users. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless B2C Jewels gives prior notice and choice. 

**Opt-Out Policy**   
To opt out of receiving communications from B2C Jewels, just send a blank email to info@b2cjewels.com with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line. 

**Updating Personal Information**   
If the personal information B2C Jewels has gathered from you changes or you no longer desire our service, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any personal data you have previously provided to us. To request a change or removal of your personal information, send an e-mail to info@b2cjewels.com or contact one of our diamond and jewelry consultants at 1 800 210 0223. 

**Security**   
B2C Jewels is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. To protect the information you send from your computer to B2C Jewels's e-commerce system, this information — including your credit card number, name, and address — is encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. Internally, we use encryption and Web security technologies to protect the privacy of your personal data. Only parties responsible for processing your order have access to your credit card and bank information. 

B2C Jewels continuously reviews its policies and practices to ensure that all customer information remains secure. 

**Use of Technology**   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer hard drive. You must have cookies enabled in order for you to be able to perform many of the general functions on the B2C Jewels Web site. With cookies enabled, the B2C Jewels Web site will have the capacity to deliver you a more customized and complete shopping experience to track visits from our affiliates and partners and to enable the use of our shopping cart. B2C Jewels does not use cookies to store or collect any personal information such as names, addresses, or payment information. To learn how to enable cookies on your computer, visit the Web site that corresponds to the browser you use: 

**IP Address**   
B2C Jewels collects your IP address, which cannot be used to identify you personally, to help diagnose problems with its server, to administer and tune the operation of its site, and to log your browser type and referring URL information. B2C Jewels's servers use each IP address to anonymously track the date and duration of each session within its site. Your IP address may also be used to help B2C Jewels collect statistical data or in gathering broad usage information. Certain parts of this information may be shared with B2C Jewels partners, but your IP address will not be distributed. 

**Contacting B2CJewels**   
To provide the best customer service possible, B2C Jewels provides multiple methods for customers to ask questions and provide feedback. 

**Contact Us**  
Via the "Contact Us" link, B2C Jewels allows customers to e-mail info@b2cjewels.com. This provides direct contact to a B2C Jewels diamond and jewelry consultant, who reads each e-mail and tries to promptly answer your questions. B2C Jewels may also file your comments to improve the site and program or review and discard the information. You may also send us your comments about the B2C Jewels Web site or the shopping experience in general, as we always appreciate feedback. 

**Fraudulent Charge Protection**   
If a third party obtains your personal information from a purchase made with B2C Jewels and uses that information to perpetrate credit card fraud, you are protected. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank may hold you liable for up to $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank holds you liable for any portion of the $50, B2C Jewels will cover up to the entire $50.* 

**Legal Disclaimer**   
The only time B2C Jewels will disclose personal information is when required to by law or with the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the law. 

If you have questions about this privacy statement, please contact the B2C Jewels customer service department at [info@b2cjewels.com](mailto:info@b2cjewels.com) or at 1 800 210 0223. 

* B2C Jewels will cover this liability if the unauthorized use resulted through no fault of yours from purchases made on B2C Jewels's secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card company in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. 

******Updated February 7, 2005**
